Guide to the Pierce and Bickford records,1890-1960.
Pierce and Bickford records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Pierce and Bickford records, 1890-1960.
2299
Pierce and Bickford (Firm).
55 cubic feet, 27 Mapcase Folders.
Correspondence, Financial Records, Legal Documents, Photographs
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Office correspondence, bills, receipts, contracts, job indexes, photographs, blueprints, and detail drawings
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence consists of both outgoing (51 letter impression books, 1899-1926) and incoming letters (131 letterboxes, ca. 1892-ca. 1931) to and from clients, contractors, and supply companies in regard to the design and construction of schools, churches, private homes, apartment houses, commercial establishments, hospitals, public buildings, and other structures in New York, New Jersey, and Pennsylvania, including the stairs and stone walls at Watkins Glen (1908), the Arnot Art Gallery, the Corning Glass Works, Cortland County and Arnot-Ogden Hospitals, the Elmira College Library, Elmira Y.M.C.A. and Masonic Temple, and the Elmira Free Academy; also, bills, receipts, contracts, indexes (2 volumes) of jobs, and various photographs, blueprints, and detail drawings.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Pierce and Bickford (Firm).; Arnot Art Gallery.; Arnot-Ogden Hospital.; Corning Glass Works.; Cortland County Hospital.; Elmira College.; Elmira Free Academy.; Elmira YMCA (Elmira, N.Y.); Masonic Temple (Elmira, N.Y.)
Subjects:
Architecture.
Places:
New York, New Jersey, Pennsylvania - Buildings.
Form and Genre Terms:
Architectural drawings.; Blueprints.; Photographs.; Correspondence, Bills, Receipts.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. 51 Letterbooks - Copies of Outgoing Correspondence, 1899 - 1926
Volumes 16-22, 24-65, 68
1. Letterbooks of Note
2. Letterbooks
Series II. Incoming letters, bills, receipts and related items
Boxes 1-131
Series III. Job file drawings, #5-1791
Box 133-148, 153; Mapcase Folders 1-18
This series is arranged alphabetically by the location of the job: first by state, then by city, and finally by the name of the project.
Plans for related buildings have often been grouped together.
1. Roselle Park, NJ; Albany - Eddytown, NY
2. Elmira, NY
3. Elmira Heights - Whitney Point, NY
4. Athens-Wyalusing, PA
Series IV. Recent correspondence, Bickford genealogy, photographs, printed material
Box 149
Series V. Job Index, Photographs, Cartoons etc.
Box 150
Series VI. Glass slides, Printing blocks, Glass plate negatives, etc.
Box 132, 151
CONTAINER LIST
- Letterbooks - Copies of Outgoing Correspondence, 1899-1926
  Fifty-one MSS. volumes of letterbooks containing copies of the outgoing correspondence
  of the architectural firm of Pierce & Bickford of Elmira, New York.
  Includes letters to clients,as well as to contractors and supply companies, in regard
  to the design and construction of buildings in New York, Pennsylvania, and New Jersey.
  Among the outstanding jobs are:
  - Letterbooks of Note
    - Apartment Buildings
    - Church and Main Streets, Elmira, for Mrs. Julia Reynolds. See correspondence in Volume (Letterbook) 17 (Volume 17)
    - Businesses
    - Allegany County Cheese Company, Wellsville. (Volume 18)
    - American-LaFrance Fire Engine Company, Elmira. (Volume 28)
    - Banks - First National of Elmira. (Volume 18)
    - Corning Glass Works. (Volume 1)
    - Elmira Knitting Mills. (Volume 16)
    - Realty Building, Elmira. (Volume 18)
    - Smith's Opera House, Geneva. (Volume 18)
    - Sun Publishing Company, Alfred. (Volume 19)
    - Churches
    - First Presbyterian Church of Bath. (Volume 51)
    - First Presbyterian Church of Dundee. (Volume 64)
    - First Presbyterian Church of Elmira. (Volume 27)
    - First Presbyterian Church of Hornell. (Volume 51)
    - First Presbyterian Church of McGraw. (Volume 20)
    - Hedding Methodist Church, Elmira. (Volume 16)
    - Memorial Church, Bellona, New York. (Volume 20)
    - Painted Post Baptist. (Volume 56)
    - Private Homes
    - Eugene Diven of Elmira. (Volume 17)
    - Judge Parkhurst of Bath. (Volume 24)
    - Hospitals
    - Allegany County Tuberculosis Hospital. (Volume 61)
    - Arnot-Ogden, Elmira. (Volume 18)
    - Cattaraugus County Tuberculosis Hospital. (Volume 54)
    - Champlain Valley Hospital, Plattsburg. (Volume 29)
    - Chemung County Tuberculosis Hospital. (Volume 59)
    - Clifton Springs Sanitarium. (Volume 16)
    - Cortland Hospital. (Volume 27)
    - Good Samaritan, Westfield, Pa. (Volume 65)
    - Glen Springs, Watkins. (Volume 16)
    - Robert Packer, Sayre, Pa. (Volume 20)
    - Steuben County Tuberculosis Hospital (Volume 59)
    - Public Buildings
    - Allegany County Jail. (Volume 47)
    - Bath Jail. (Volume 29)
    - Elmira City Hall. (Volume 38)
    - Hornell Court House. (Volume 32)
    - Painted Post Town Hall. (Volume 62)
    - Sayre Town Hall. (Volume 32)
    - Steele Memorial Library, Elmira. (Volume 18)
    - Yates County Home. (Volume 65)
    - Organization Buildings
    - Century Club, Elmira. (Volume 29)
    - National Protective Legion Building, Waverly, N. Y. (Volume 21)
    - Masonic Temple, Elmira. (Volume 55)
    - Masonic Temple, Kane, Pa. (Volume 17)
    - Masonic Temple, Wellsville, N. Y. (Volume 61)
    - Masonic Temple, Westfield, Pa. (Volume 21)
    - Y. M. C. A., Elmira. (Volume 65)
    - Y. M. C. A, Geneva, N. Y. (Volume 21)
    - School Buildings
    - Andover, New York. (Volume 24)
    - Angelica, N. Y. (Volume 34)
    - Athens, Pa. (Volume 54)
    - Belfast, N. Y. (Volume 50)
    - Bradford, Pa. (Volume 16)
    - Candor, N. Y. (Volume 35)
    - Cazenovia Seminary. (Volume 18)
    - Chatham, N. Y. (Volume 51)
    - Cortland. N. Y. (Volume 29)
    - Cuba, N. Y. (Volume 34)
    - Delhi, N. Y. (Volume 57)
    - Dryden, N. Y. (Volume 36)
    - East Rochester, N. Y. (Volume 42)
    - Elmira - Elmira Free Academy. (Volume 41)
    - Elmira South Side High School. (Volume 64)
    - Elmira Heights, N. Y. (Volume 31)
    - Falconer, N. Y. (Volume 8)
    - Franklinville, N. Y. (Volume 50)
    - Friendship, N. Y. (Volume 30)
    - Knoxville, Pa. (Volume 19)
    - Manchester, N. Y. (Volume 50)
    - Mansfield Normal School. (Volume 47)
    - Olean, N. Y. (Volume 57)
    - Owego, New York. (Volume 27)
    - Penn Yan, N. Y. (Volume 68)
    - Rochester, N. Y. (Volume 49)
    - Roselle Park, N. J. (Volume 49)
    - Toms River, N. J. (Volume 19)
    - Tully, N. Y. (Volume 18)
    - Warsaw, N. Y. (Volume 48)
    - Watkins, N. Y. (Volume 64)
    - Waverly, N. Y. (Volume 50)
    - Whitney Point, N. Y. (Volume 19)
  - Letterbooks
    - Letterbook 16, May 31, 1899-Jan 26, 1900 (Volume 16)
    - Letterbook 17, Jan. 26, 1900-Oct. 10, 190 (Volume 17)
    - Letterbook 18, Oct. 10, 1900-Apr. 11, 1901 (Volume 18)
    - Letterbook 19, Apr. 12, 1901-Dec. 3, 1901 (Volume 19)
    - Letterbook 20, Dec. 3, 1902-June 19, 1302 (Volume 20)
    - Letterbook 21, June 19, 1902-Jan. 16, 1903 (Volume 21)
    - Letterbook 22, Jan. 16, 1903-July 31, 1903 (Volume 22)
    - Letterbook 24, Aug. 1, 1903-March 10, 1904 (Volume 24)
    - Letterbook 25, March 9, 1904-Nov. 19, 1904 (Volume 25)
    - Letterbook 26, Nov. 22, 1904-Aug 29, 1905 (Volume 26)
    - Letterbook 27, Aug. 29, 1905-May 18, 1906 (Volume 27)
    - Letterbook 28, May 19, 1906-Jan. 3, 1907 (Volume 28)
    - Letterbook 29, Jan. 3, 1907-June 11, 1907 (Volume 29)
    - Letterbook 30, June 11, 1907-0ct. 25, 1907 (Volume 30)
    - Letterbook 31, Oct. 25, 1907-Feb. 14, 1908 (Volume 31)
    - Letterbook 32, Feb. 14, 1905-June 9, 1909 (Volume 32)
    - Letterbook 33, June 9, 1908-Sept. 20, 1908 (Volume 33)
    - Letterbook 34, Sept. 30, 1908-Feb. 23, 1909 (Volume 34)
    - Letterbook 35, Feb. 24, 1909-June 14, 1909 (Volume 35)
    - Letterbook 36, June 16, 1909-Oct. 2, 1909 (Volume 36)
    - Letterbook 37, Oct. 4, 1909-Feb. 25, 1910 (Volume 37)
    - Letterbook 38, Feb. 26, 1910-June 28, 1910 (Volume 38)
    - Letterbook 39, June 28, 1910-0ct. 18, 1910 (Volume 39)
    - Letterbook 40, Oct. 19, 1910-March 24, 1911 (Volume 40)
    - Letterbook 41, March 23, 1911-July 15, 1911 (Volume 41)
    - Letterbook 42, July 15, 191-Aug. 31, 1911 (Volume 42)
    - Letterbook 43, Oct. 26, 1911-Feb. 9, 1912 (Volume 43)
    - Letterbook 44, Feb. 9, 1912-May 11, 1912 (Volume 44)
    - Letterbook 45, May 11, 1912-Aug. 17, 1912 (Volume 45)
    - Letterbook 46, Aug. 20, 1912-Dec. 10, 1912 (Volume 46)
    - Letterbook 47, Dec. 10, 1912-April 7, 1913 (Volume 47)
    - Letterbook 48, April 9, 1913 -Aug. I4, 1913 (Volume 48)
    - Letterbook 49, Aug. 14, 1913-Dec. 31, 1913 (Volume 49)
    - Letterbook 50, Dec. 31, 1913-April 26, 1914 (Volume 50)
    - Letterbook 51, April 25, 1914-Aug 20, 1914 (Volume 51)
    - Letterbook 52, Aug. 20, 1914-Dec. l4, 1914 (Volume 52)
    - Letterbook 53, Dec. 14, 1914-Aprll 2, 1915 (Volume 53)
    - Letterbook 54, April 3, 1915-July 12, 1915 (Volume 54)
    - Letterbook 55, July 12, 1915-Nov. 1, 1915 (Volume 55)
    - Letterbook 56, Nov. 1, 1915-March 19, 1916 (Volume 56)
    - Letterbook 57, March 70, 1916-Aug. 13, 1916 (Volume 57)
    - Letterbook 58, Aug. 12, 1916-Feb.20, 1917 (Volume 58)
    - Letterbook 59, Feb. 20, 1917-Dec. 19, 1917 (Volume 59)
    - Letterbook 60, Dec. 20, 1917-April 23, 1919 (Volume 60)
    - Letterbook 61, April 24, 1919-Dec. 18, 1919 (Volume 61)
    - Letterbook 62, Dec. 19, 1919-0ct. 25, 1920 (Volume 62)
    - Letterbook 63, Oct. 27, 1920-Nov. 10, 1921 (Volume 63)
    - Letterbook 64, Nov. 10, 192l-Oct. 27, 1922 (Volume 64)
    - Letterbook 65, Oct. 27, 1922-Aug. 20, 1922 (Volume 65)
    - Letterbook 67 marked "Arnot Art Gallery", Bills paid, Dec. 22, 1911-Aug. 22, 1925 (Volume 67)
      Note on cover: From July 17, 1913: Bills paid
    - Letterbook 68, April 29, 1925-Jan 12, 1926 (Volume 68)
- Incoming letters, bills, receipts and related items, 1892-1931
  The numbers in parentheses refer to numbers sometimes written on the backs of the letterboxes
  - Letters, many related to processes for strengthening steel (marked 1896 H.H.B.), c.1896-c.1905 (Box 1)
  - Mainly bills (4), Jan. 1892-Aug. 1895 (Box 2)
  - Bills and receipts, l898-1906 (Box 3)
  - Plattsburg Hospital, c.1903-c.1904 (Box 4)
  - Bids (4), c.1904-c.1906 (Box 5)
  - Bids (5), June 1907-June 1909 (Box 6)
  - Bids (6), June 1909-December 1910 (Box 7)
  - Receipts (3), May 1910-November l912 (Box 8)
  - Letters, December 1904-November 1910 (Box 9)
  - Letters (56), October 1910-Deccember 1910 (Box 10)
  - Bids (7), December 1910-June 1912 (Box 11)
  - Letters (57), December 1910-April 1911 (Box 12)
  - Letters (58), April 1911 (Box 13)
  - Letters (59), June 1911 (Box 14)
  - Letters (60), September 1911-January 1912 (Box 15)
  - Letters (61), January-March 1912 (Box 16)
  - Letters (62), March-June 1912 (Box 17)
  - Letters (63), June-August 1912 (Box 18)
  - Letters (64), August-October 1912 (Box 19)
  - Letters, Arnot Art Gallery (1), c.February-August 1912 (Box 20)
  - Letters, Arnot Art Gallery (2), c.April 1912-c.November 1913 (Box 21)
  - Letters (65), October-December 1912 (Box 22)
  - Receipts (4), November 1912-July 1916 (Box 23)
  - Completed Contracts (5), c.1912-c.1914 (Box 24)
  - Completed Contracts (24), February 1907-December 1913 (Box 25)
    Also contains a contract dated December 1896
  - Bids, June 1912-September 1913 (Box 26)
  - Letters (66), December 1912-February 1913 (Box 27)
  - Letters (67), February-April 1913 (Box 28)
  - Letters (68), April-July 1913 (Box 29)
  - Letters (69), July-September 1913 (Box 30)
  - Letters (70), September-October 1913 (Box 31)
  - Letters (71), October 1913-Janaury 1914 (Box 32)
  - Bids (9), September 1913-November 1914 (Box 33)
  - Letters (72), January-February 1914 (Box 34)
  - Letters (73), February-March 1914 (Box 35)
  - Letters (74), March-May 1914 (Box 36)
  - Letters (75), May-June 1914 (Box 37)
  - Letters (76), June-August 1914 (Box 38)
  - Letters (77), August-October 1914 (Box 39)
  - Letters (78), October-December 1914 (Box 40)
  - Bids (10), December 1914-July 1915 (Box 41)
  - Completed Contracts (6), c.1914-c.1916 (Box 42)
  - Letters (79), December 1914-February 1915 (Box 43)
  - Letters (80), February-April 1915 (Box 44)
  - Letters (81), April-May 1915 (Box 45)
  - Letters (82), May-June 1915 (Box 46)
  - Letters (83), June-August 1915 (Box 47)
  - Letters (84), August-October 1915 (Box 48)
  - Letters (85), October-December 1915 (Box 49)
  - Letters (86), December 1915-February 1916 (Box 50)
  - Bids (11), July 1915--4ugust 1916 (Box 51)
  - Letters (87), February-April 1916 (Box 52)
  - Letters (88), April-June 1916 (Box 53)
  - Letters (89), June-July 1916 (Box 54)
  - Letters (90), July-September 1916 (Box 55)
  - Letters (91), September-October 1916 (Box 56)
  - Letters (92), October 1916-January 1917 (Box 57)
  - Letters (93), January-May 1917 (Box 58)
  - Letters (94), May-October 1917 (Box 59)
  - Bids (12), August 1916-August 1917 (Box 60)
  - Receipts (5), July 1916-January 1922 (Box 61)
  - Letters (95), October 1917-November 1918 (Box 62)
  - Bills, Receipts (2), c.1914-c.1917 (Box 63)
  - Bills, Receipts (3), October 1917-1924 (Box 64)
  - Letters (96), November 1918-June 1919 (Box 65)
  - Bids (13), August 1917-1920 (Box 66)
  - Estate of R. T. Turner, previous to October 1, 1919 (Box 67)
  - Letters (97), June-November 1919 (Box 68)
  - Letters (98), November 1919-April 1920 (Box 69)
  - Bids (14), January 1920-January 1921 (Box 70)
  - Letters (99), April 1920-January 1921 (Box 71)
  - Letters (100), January-August 1921 (Box 72)
  - Bids (15), January 1921-January 1922 (Box 73)
  - Bids (16), January 1922-1924 (Box 74)
  - Letters (101), August 1921-January 1922 (Box 75)
  - Letters (102), January-June 1922 (Box 76)
  - Receipts (6), January 1922-March 1926 (Box 77)
  - Letters, No.1, The Elmira Southside High School, February-July 1922 (Box 78)
  - Letters, No.2, The Elmira Southside High School, July 1922-January 1923 (Box 79)
  - Letters, No.3, The Elmira Southside High School, January 1923-January 1924 (Box 80)
  - Letters (103), June 1922-February 1923 (Box 81)
  - Letters, No.1, S. F. Iszard Company, October-November 1922 (Box 82)
  - Letters, No.2, S. F. Iszard Company, November 1923-August 1924 (Box 83)
  - Letters (104), February-June 1923 (Box 84)
  - Letters (105), June-November 1923 (Box 85)
  - Letters, No.1, Y. M. C. A. Building, October 1922-November 1923 (Box 86)
  - Letters, No.2, Y. M. C. A. Building, November 1923-February 1925 (Box 87)
  - Letters (106), November 1923-February 1925 (Box 88)
  - Letters, Allegany County Home, December 1923-c. November 1926 (Box 89)
  - Letters, No.1, Elmira College Library, December 1923-c.December 1926 (Box 90)
  - Bills, S.F. Iszard Company, F.H. Johnston, Bills Nos.1, 2 & 3, December 15 & 21, 1923, February 2, 1924 (Box 91)
  - Bids (17), January 1924-c.April 1926 (Box 92)
  - Letters No.4, The Elmira Southside High School, January-c. December 1924 (Box 93)
  - Letters No.1, Clifton Springs Sanitarium, February 1924-May 1925 (Box 94)
  - S. F. Iszard Company No.3, August 1924-c. December 1925 (Box 95)
  - Letters (107), February-December 1925 (Box 96)
  - Letters, No.3, Y.M.C.A. Building, February 1925-March 1926 (Box 97)
  - Letters No.2, Clifton Springs Sanitarium, May 1925-c.June 1926 (Box 98)
  - Letters, Arnot Ogden Hospital Nurses' Home, June 1925-c.April 1929 (Box 99)
  - Letters (108), December 1925-February 1927 (Box 100)
  - Letters, No.1, Elmira School No. 11, December 1925-c. March 1927 (Box 101)
  - Letters, No.1, Ontario County Home, January 1926-February 1927 (Box 102)
  - Estate of R.T. Turner, 1926 (Box 103)
  - Letters, Cortland County Hospital Annex, September 1926-c.June 1928 (Box 104)
  - Letters, Starkey Seminary, 1926-1929 (Box 105)
  - Letters, No.2, Ontario County Home, February 1927-c.November 1930 (Box 106)
  - Letters (109), February-July 1927 (Box 107)
  - Letters (110), July 1927-February 1928 (Box 108)
  - Letters, No.1, Second National Bank, 1927 (Box 109)
  - Special, Second National Bank, 1927-1929 (Box 110)
  - Letters, S. N. B., 1927-1929 (Box 111)
  - Letters, No.2, S. K. B., 1927-1929 (Box 112)
  - Letters, Cook Academy, March 1928-c. January 1929 (Box 113)
  - Letters (111), February 1928-April 1929 (Box 114)
  - Letters, Turner Estate Building, June 1928-January 1930 (Box 115)
  - Letters, Annex to Hedding M. E. Church, September 1928-c.June 1930 (Box 116)
  - Letters, No.1, (Elmira Heights) High and Grade School, September 1928-November 1929 (Box 117)
  - Letters No.2, Elmira H. H. and G. School, November 1929-c.August 1931 (Box 118)
  - Letters, Chemung Grade School, 1929 (Box 119)
  - Letters, No. 3 School, January 1929-April 1930 (Box 120)
  - Letters, No. 3 School, April 1930-c.February 1931 (Box 121)
  - Letters, Centenary Church (M. E., Elmira), 1929-1930 (Box 122)
  - Letters, Millport School, 1930 (Box 123)
  - Letters, Huguet Silk Company Annex to Dye House, 1930 (Box 124)
  - Letters, Gorton Building, 1931-1932 (Box 125)
  - Letters, Corning Glass Works No.1, 1911 (Box 126)
  - Letters, Corning Glass Works No. 2, 1911-1912 (Box 127)
  - Letters, Corning Glass Works No.3, c.1911-c.1912 (Box 128)
  - Contract File, Job#s 1072, 1100s, 1200s (not complete) (4) (Box 129)
  - Completed Contracts, Job#s 1300s, 1400s (not complete) (7) (Box 130)
  - Contracts, Job#s 1492, 1500s (not complete) (8) (Box 131)
- Job file drawings (Box 133-148)
  - Roselle Park, NJ; Albany - Eddytown, NY
    - Roselle Park, NJ (Box 136)
      High School
      Job# 1078
    - Albany, NY (Box 133)
      Univ. SNY, Rural school Building
      Job# 59
    - Andover, NY (Box 135)
      School House
      Job# 875
    - Angelica, NY (Box 142)
      Allegany County Home
      Job# 1521
    - Angelica, NY (Box 142)
      Allegany County Home, Dormitory
      Job# 1373 (with Job# 1521)
    - Angelica, NY (Box 136)
      Wilsonian High School
      Job# 1121
    - Arkport, NY (Box 143)
      Arkport Creamery
      Job# 1567
    - Bath, NY (Box 134)
      Centenary M. E. Church
      Job# 826
    - Bath, NY (Box 142)
      Bath Court House, vault
      Job# 1225 (with Job# 1527)
    - Bath, NY (Box 142)
      County Clerk's Office
      Job# 954 (with Job# 1527)
    - Bath, NY (Box 142)
      Job# 1455 (with Job# 1527)
    - Bath, NY (Box 142)
      Steuben County Jail Office & Ct. Hs.
      Job# 1408 (with Job# 1527)
    - Bath, NY (Box 142)
      Steuben County Tuberculosis Hospital
      Job# 1357 (with Job# 1527)
    - Bath, NY (Box 142)
      Job# 1367 (with Job# 1527)
    - Bath, NY (Box 142)
      Steuben County Jail
      Job# 1038 (with Job# 1527)
    - Bath, NY (Box 142)
      Steuben County Court House
      Job# 1021 (with Job# 1527)
    - Bath, NY (Box 142)
      Job# 1104 (with Job# 1527)
    - Belfast, NY (Box 139)
      Union School
      Job# 1247
    - Bellona, NY (Box 134)
      Presbyterian Church
      Job# 433
    - Belmont, NY (Box 142)
      Allegany County Hospital
      Job# 1382 (with Job# 1521)
    - Belmont, NY (Box 142)
      Allegany County Jail
      Job# 1215 (with Job# 1521)
    - Belmont, NY (Box 142)
      Allegany County Offices
      Job# 1162 (with Job# 1521)
    - Belmont, NY (Box 142)
      Construction not used
      Job# 1162-A (with Job# 1521)
    - Big Flats, NY (Box 139)
      Presbyterian Church, parsonage
      Job# 1238
    - Big Flats, NY (Box 142)
      Alterations to Presbyterian Church
      Job# 1498
    - Binghamton, NY (Box 134)
      Cleaves, W. B. (Austin Estate)
      Job# 569
    - Buffalo, NY (Box 148)
      Elmwood Ave.
      Job# 1772-B
    - Canandaigua, NY (Box 143)
      Ontario County Almshouse
      Job# 1555
    - Cattaraugus County, NY (Box 140)
      Tuberculosis Hospital
      Job# 1309
    - Chatham, NY (Box 139)
      Job# 1286
    - Chemung, NY (Box 145)
      Chemung School Building
      Job# 1588
    - Clifton Springs, NY (Box 143)
      Sanitarium
      Job# 758 (with Job# 1539)
    - Clifton Springs, NY (Box 143)
      Sanitarium, servants quarters
      Job# 1165 (with Job# 1539)
    - Clifton Springs, NY (Box 143)
      Job# 1180 (with Job# 1539)
    - Clifton Springs, NY (Box 143)
      Job# 1432 (with Job# 1539)
    - Clifton Springs, NY (Box 143)
      Job# 359, 578, 1468, 1539
    - Clifton Springs, NY (Box 143)
      Perspective drawing: Prints from wood block in box with glass slides.
      Job# none given
    - Corning, NY (Box 133)
      Baptist Church
      Job# 9
    - Corning, NY, 1910-1911 (Folder 14-16)
      Corning Glass Works
      Job# 1195
    - Corning, NY (Box 145)
      Corning Hotel
      Job# 1594
    - Corning, NY (Box 146)
      Corning Leader Inc.
      Job# 1716
    - Corning, NY (Box 140)
      Hawkes, T.G. & Company, Building
      Job# 1306
    - Corning, NY (Box 147)
      Pinkston, Dr. C.J., residence
      Job# 1732
    - Corning, NY (Box 148)
      Underhill, W. Allen, residence
      Job# 1762
    - Corning, NY (Box 135)
      Wing & Bostwick Building
      Job# 864
    - Cortland, NY (Box 138)
      Baptist Society, parsonage
      Job# 1205
    - Cortland, NY (Box 137)
      Bauder, Delos, residence
      Job# 1127
    - Cortland, NY (Box 144)
      Cortland County Hospital
      Job# 1113, 1570
    - Cortland, NY (Box 136)
      Masonic Temple
      Job# 1100
    - Cortland, NY (Box 136)
      School building
      Job# 1044
    - Cortland, NY (Box 147)
      St. Mary's Church
      Job# 1743
    - Cortland, NY (Box 138)
      Wickwire, Charles C., residence
      Job# 1220
    - Cortland, NY (Box 137)
      York Hotel
      Job# 1167
    - Cuba, NY (Box 137)
      Cuba School
      Job# 1138
    - Delhi, NY (Box 145)
      Delhi Telephone Company Building
      Job# 1612
    - Delhi, NY (Box 140)
      High School Building
      Job# 1303
    - Dundee, NY (Box 133)
      Dundee Baptist Church
      Job# 7
    - Dundee, NY (Box 133)
      Olivet Baptist Church
      Job# 6
    - Dundee, NY (Box 133)
      Job# 5
    - Dundee, NY (Box 133)
      School Building
      Job# 8
    - East Rochester, NY (Box 137)
      Job# 1184
    - Eddytown, NY (Box 134)
      School
      Job# 730
  - Elmira, NY
    - American LaFrance Fire Engine Company (Box 146)
      Job# 935,950,979, 996, 1003 (with Job# 1730)
    - American LaFrance Fire Engine Company (Box 146)
      Job# 1020, 1020 A-P (with Job# 1730)
    - American LaFrance Fire Engine Company (Box 146)
      Job# 1233, 1245 (with Job# 1730)
    - American LaFrance Fire Engine Company (Box 147)
      Job# 1318 (with Job# 1730)
    - American LaFrance Fire Engine Company (Box 147)
      Job# 1624,1645,1654,1658,1661,1663,1669, 1671,1674,
      1675-1678,1680,1682,1684,1686,1689,1689-A,1691,1692 (with Job# 1730)
    - American LaFrance Fire Engine Company (Box 146)
      Job# 1728,1730
    - Arnot Ogden Memorial Hospital (Box 147)
      Job# 1298-B (with Job# 1736)
    - Arnot Ogden Nurses Home (Box 147)
      Job# 1544 (with Job# 1736)
    - Arnot Ogden Hospital (Box 147)
      Job# 1632 (with Job# 1736)
    - Arnot-Ogden Memorial Hospital (Box 147)
      Job# 1736, 1736-A
    - Baker, Charles S. (Box 140)
      Job# 1326
    - Baldwin, F. E., residence (Box 134)
      Job# 470
    - Barker, Rose & Clinton warehouse (Box 140)
      Job# 1317
    - Barker, Rose & Clinton Company (Box 141)
      Job# 1433
    - Blackmore-Danzig Building (Box 145)
      Job# 1599
      Full Size Details: Showing relation of Sidewalk and Foundation
      Plaster Cornice and Pilaster Caps
      Sill for Steel Windows
      Profile for Brackets
      Cap Stones for Piers
      2nd and 3rd Floor Windows
      Stone Members Over Mezzanine Windows rev. 7-2-1930
      Details of Corner Entrance
      Stone Details rev. 9-30-1930
    - Blysonte, F.M., residence (Box 135)
      Job# 914
    - Booth, D r. Arthur, residence (Box 141)
      Job# 1441
    - Booth, I. D., warehouse (Box 136)